<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on neap space</title><link>/posts/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on neap space</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0600</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Deep Dive: Cloud Backup for Slow Connections, Part II</title><link>/2021/04/deep-dive-cloud-backup-for-slow-connections-part-ii/</link><pubDate>Fri, 16 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>/2021/04/deep-dive-cloud-backup-for-slow-connections-part-ii/</guid><description>This is the second post in my deep dive series on cloud backup for network attached storage (NAS). In this article, I&amp;rsquo;ll walk through preparing the test machine and the tools I used to evaluate candidate backup clients
If you&amp;rsquo;re not interested in kvm or shell scripts and just want the results, you might want to skip to the next part. However, if you&amp;rsquo;re new to setting up virtual machines and ZFS or are interested in doing similar testing, keep reading to see what I did.</description></item><item><title>Deep Dive: Cloud Backup for Slow Connections, Part I</title><link>/2021/04/deep-dive-cloud-backup-for-slow-connections-part-i/</link><pubDate>Mon, 05 Apr 2021 00:00:00 -0600</pubDate><guid>/2021/04/deep-dive-cloud-backup-for-slow-connections-part-i/</guid><description>For detailed steps, scripts, and results, you can follow along with the GitHub repo that accompanies this series of articles here: neapsix/cloudbackup-benchmarks.
In case further proof were needed, last month&amp;rsquo;s story about the companies that lost irreplaceable data in a literal towering inferno proves again that everyone with important files needs offsite backups. I don&amp;rsquo;t mean to make fun of the hosting provider or the companies who got caught without backups in multiple locations (OK, maybe them, a little bit).</description></item></channel></rss>